diffordsguide.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how Odd Firm of Sin Ltd (trading as 'Difford's Guide') collects and processes your personal information through your use of our website, including any data you may provide through this website and when you sign up to our newsletter.

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. We will always communicate any changes to you, where we have accurate contact details. Please visit this section of our website periodically in order to keep up to date with changes in our privacy policy.

If you have any questions relating to this privacy policy please contact us at [info@diffordsguide.com](mailto:info@diffordsguide.com).

### 1\. About us

Odd Firm of Sin Ltd is a UK based publisher, registered in England and Wales, company number 03365966. We publish this website, diffordsguide.com, and a range of books.

### 2\. Information we collect about you

We may collect, use and store different kinds of information about you when you register for our newsletter and / or an account, submit your information to join event guest lists or enter cocktail competitions, submit a job or product listing, which we have grouped together as follows:

  * Identity Data includes first name, last name and date of birth.
  * Contact Data includes address, email address and telephone number.
  * Transaction Data includes details about products and services you have purchased from us such as a job advert or product listing.
  * Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location.
  * Profile Data includes your preferences such as whether you prefer to receive our trade or consumer newsletter and your favourite cocktails.
  * Usage Data includes information about how you use our website.
  * Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving our newsletter.

### 3\. How we collect your data

We collect different information about you in a number of ways:

**Information you give us**

When you create an account on our website, sign up to our newsletter, enter cocktail competitions, sign up to event guest lists or order a product or service, we will store the personal information you give to us such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number.

**Automated technologies or interactions**

As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies and other similar technologies.

### 4\. How may we use your information

We use the personal information that you directly provide to us for the following purposes:

  * To send you our email newsletter
  * To allow you to log into your personal diffordsguide.com account

We use non-personally identifiable information (such as links you click on) to improve our site. We may aggregate parts of this data and share this information in an anonymous form with our third-party partners. This data will not contain any personally identifiable information.

### 5\. Disclosure of your details to third-parties

There are certain circumstances under which we may disclose your personal information to third-parties. These are as follows:

  * To our third-party partners who are running events or cocktail competitions, to enable them to administer their event guest list or competition. We require all third-parties to respect the privacy of your personal information and to treat it in accordance with the law and we protect you by requiring them to formerly contract accordingly. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal information for their own purposes unless you have expressly opted in to receive information from them and only permit them to process your personal information for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.
  * Where we are under a duty to disclose your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation (for example to government bodies and law enforcement agencies).

We do not sell personal details to third-parties for any purpose.

### 6\. Security of your personal information

We have put in place appropriate safeguards (both in terms of our procedures and the technology we use) to keep your personal information as secure as possible. Third-parties will also be subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We will not transfer, process or store your data anywhere that is outside of the European Economic Area, unless we have a contractual agreement in place that is of an equivalent standard to GDPR.

### 7\. Data retention

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including to satisfy any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

### 8\. Where we store your information

We store your information on servers in the UK and Ireland.

### 9\. How to request or delete the information we store about you

If you would like to request the information we store about you, or to have your information deleted, please email us at info@diffordsguide.com

### 10\. Links to other sites

Difford's Guide may create links allowing you to access third-party sites such as Amazon in order to purchase products. Please read those sites' individual privacy policies to see how they use your data.

### 11\. Contact details and further information

Please get in touch with us if you have any questions about any aspect of this privacy policy.

Please also contact us if you have any questions about the information we hold about you, or to delete or change your contact preferences with us:

Email us: info@diffordsguide.com

Write to us:

Odd Firm of Sin Ltd  
The Clocktower  
Sherbourne Valley, Hastings Road  
Rye  
TN31 6HY  
United Kingdom. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 25 May 2018.

Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
